Contact

deirdre_lee@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/deirdre-murdoch-76218426 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing ACLS Emergency Room

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
French (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Limited Working)

Certifications ACLS

Deirdre Murdoch

ER/TRAUMA NURSE at Doctors Hospital at Renaissance Health System

McAllen, Texas Area

Summary

I am a straight forward mature RN who started from a Medical floor to the advanced life support in very busy ER/Trauma centers . I have 15 years experience in care, compassion and take my work seriously and am very passionate about my work as a care giver. Whether in the capacity of a hospital or the community offering my time to visit less fortunate people who are unable to seek medical care outside the home. My desire is to continue to help as many people as I am able to do in this lifetime to make others safe and healthy with the God given knowledge I have. I have never been more satisfied as I am in the nursing field. Through education, and teaching people can feel like they are in control of their lives and take responsibility for their health.

Spent two years in Cameco, Key Lake, as an occupational health nurse. Part of my job was to educate different team members with regards to their health, their medication, and was part of a collaborative safety program. Provided employees and contractors with information pertaining to their specific needs and health issues. Work directly with the safety department to ensure each employee worked safely with in the workplace. Created fun and educational ways to learn about health while encouraging participation in group activities.

I am a retired veteran (licensed mechanic) of the Canadian Armed Forces. I spent 8 years as a Social Worker in Alberta. Spent several months traveling in and around the area with the honorable Jack Shields from Fort McMurray working with him and his team bringing educational supplies to northern communities.

Experience

Doctors Hospital at Renaissance Health System ER/TRAUMA NURSE

June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)

SOUTH TEXAS

Level 1 Trauma Centers are required to have immediately available all resources to stabilize and definitively treat even the most complex traumatic injuries.

AND WE DO...

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions

ER/Trauma

November 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

I am a local travel RN, working ER, Trauma and really enjoy being an Occupational Health Nurse

Consultant

Company B Task Force (Personal Advisor)

2011 - Present (9 years)

McAllen, Texas Area

Provided inspiration and motivation to individuals who are interested in career advancement and had desires for growth and development. Consultant to local businesses looking to hire drivers for various jobs whether local or long distance.

Medical Solutions

RN

September 2006 - May 2017 (10 years 9 months)

I began to work at Medical Solutions several years back and have had the best time working with Chris Wepfer! He is a wonderful recruiter and has become a great friend.

Cameco Corporation

Occupational Health Nurse

September 2011 - May 2013 (1 year 9 months)

Key Lake Saskatchewan

Managed, educated, and cared for employees and contractors at a remote uranium site. Certified Drug and Alcohol tester through Department of

Transport. Created and developed care plans for employees returning to work. Developed a disaster plan for chemical and environmental exposure.

McAllen Texas
McAllen Medical Centre
November 2008 - April 2011 (2 years 6 months)

Worked with a wonderful caring group of Trauma Nurses.

Danbury Hospital Registered Nurse 2004 - 2005 (1 year)

Worked in a surgical floor with a wonderful team of doctors and nurses.

Department of National Defence
Vehicle Technician
April 1980 - August 1987 (7 years 5 months)
CFB Borden, CFB Gagetown

I was a mechanical engineer in the Canadian Armed Forces. I loved my job, loved my career met some great people. RCEME Corp

Arte et Marte!

Education

Saint Lawrence College

Associate of Science (A.S.), Emergency Room/Trauma Nursing · (1998 - 2001)

LRHS

High School Diploma · (1975 - 1979)